A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor John G. Pollard, 1930-1934
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor John G. Pollard, 1930-1934
The Library of Virginia
23344a
57.75 cu. ft. (164 boxes)
Pollard, John G., Records of Virginia Governor
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 23344a transferred from the Office of the Governor, 1946 January and May.
Biographical Information
John Garland Pollard (1871-1937) served as attorney general of Virginia 1914-1918, and Governor of Virginia 1930-1934. He was married to Violet MacDougall Pollard (d. 1977) and is buried at Hollywood Cemetery, Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content
The Executive Papers of Governor John G. Pollard are housed in 164 boxes. The collection is arranged into six (6) series. Series have been designated for: I. General Correspondence. II. Miscellaneous Correspondence. III. Delegates Appointed. IV. Penal Affairs. V. Financial Records. VI. Personal. These records include applications, appointments, correspondence, extraditions, invitations, pardons, proclamations, reports, and requisitions. These records document the gubernatorial administration of John G. Pollard, 15 January 1930 to 16 January 1934.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. General Correspondence
Series II: Miscellaneous Correspondence
Series III: Delegates Appointed
Series IV: Penal Affairs
Series V: Financial Records
Series VI: Personal
Contents List
- Series I: General Correspondence, 1930-1934., Extent: 43.05 cu. ft. (123 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-123)
  The General Correspondence series, 1930-1934 is housed in one hundred and twenty-three archival boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. This series documents correspondence received and sent by Governor Pollard during his four-year term as governor of Virginia. In addition to correspondence, there are reports, proclamations, telegrams, orders, resolutions, acts, publications, news clippings, invitations, proceedings, financial statements, invoices, and other sundry items. Topics include Addresses and Statements, Adjutant General, Agriculture and Immigration, Apple Blossom Festival, Appointments, Art Commission, Attorney General, Budget, Buildings and Grounds, Busts in Rotunda, Conservation and Development, Corporation Commission, Education, Federal Affairs (Civilian Conservation Corps, Emergency Relief, Public Works, Reconstruction Finance Corporation), Fisheries, General Assembly, Highways, Invitations, Judges, Law Enforcement, Motor Vehicles, Penitentiary, Proclamations, Prohibition Department, Purchasing and Printing, Reorganization of State Government, State Art Museum, State Seal, Taxation, Unemployment, George Washington (Bicentennial Birth Commission), and Yorktown Sesqui-centennial Commission.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Addresses and statements (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Adjutant General (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Adjutant General (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
  - Advertising (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture and Immigration (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Commissioner (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Recommendations (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Board (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Farm Commission (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Fertilizer (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Division of Markets (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Air Tour (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - American Green Cross (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - American Legion (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - American Legislator's Association (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Taxpayer's League (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Annual reports (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Anonymous letters (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Apple Blossom Festival (Box 4, Folder 12-14)
  - Appointments (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Appointments, Delegates (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Appointments, General Assembly Recommendations (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Appointments, Requests (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Appointments, Not requiring confirmation (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Appointments, Requiring confirmation (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Appomattox monument (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Arbor Day (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Art Commission (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Art Commission (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Articles (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Associated general contractors (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta Constitution (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic University (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Attorney General (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 6, Folder 9-11)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Auditing Committee (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Autographs (Box 7, Folder 3-6)
  - Aviation (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Aviation, Airports (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Aviation, French Aviators (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Banks (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Battle Abbey (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Battlefields Memorial Commission (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Berkley Hills Boat Regatta (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bond conference (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bonds, Clintwood (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Book Publishers Research Institute (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Boundary line, Virginia and Maryland (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Bryan Memorial Association (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Budget, Director (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
  - Budget, Director (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 10% appropriation cut (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
  - Budget, Board (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Budget, Conditional Appropriations (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Editors and Publishers Conference (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Budget, Salary adjustments (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Budget, Vocational agriculture (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Buffaloes (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and grounds, Superintendent (Box 10, Folder 2-4)
  - Buildings and grounds, Bell Tower (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and grounds, Capitol building (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and grounds, Capitol guide (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and grounds, Capitol police (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and grounds, Capitol Square (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and grounds, Capitol statuary (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and grounds, Capitol tablets (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and grounds, Davis property (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and grounds, Mansion and Capitol tablets (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Bus and Truck Commission (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Busts in Rotunda (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Addresses upon unveiling (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Plates (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Harrison (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Harrison (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Jefferson (Box 12, Folder 3-6)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Madison (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Monroe (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Taylor (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Tyler (Box 13, Folder 5-7)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Washington (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Virginia Born, Wilson (Box 14, Folder 2-7)
  - Busts in Rotunda, Presidents, Programs (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Byrd, Admiral Richard E., Portrait (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Byrd, Admiral Richard E., Sword Fund (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
  - Cabinet meetings (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Camp America (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Campaigns, Democratic, State, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Campaigns, Democratic, State, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Campaigns, Democratic, National, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Campaigns, Democratic, State, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Campaigns, Democratic, Speeches (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Cape Charles Goodwill Tour (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Cape Henry Memorial Commission (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Chicago Daily News (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Children's Home Society (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - Christmas cards (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Clerk, House of Delegates (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Clippings (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Coal (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Code of Citizenship (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Commissions, Compulsory Motor Vehicle Liability Insurance and Permits (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Commissions, Regulation of Motor Vehicle Registration (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Commissions, Study of Shore and Beach Erosion (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Committee for the Nation (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Confederate Museum (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Confederate Veterans, Reunion (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Confederate Veterans (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
  - Confederate Women, Home for Needy (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Foot Guard (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Conservation and Development (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
  - Conservation and Development (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation and Development, Appalachian Electric Power Company (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Conservation and Development, Battlefield Parks (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Conservation and Development, Judge Carson's Fee (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Conservation and Development, Century of Progress (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Conservation and Development, Colonial National Park (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Conservation and Development, Geological Dept. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Conservation and Development, Landscape Engineer (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Conservation and Development, Outdoor Advertising (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Conservation and Development, Park to Park Highway (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Conservation and Development, Skyline Drive (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Conservation and Development, State Parks (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
  - Conservation and Development, Travel Bureau (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Conservation and Development, Washington Mill (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Conservation and Development, Water Power Bill (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Constitution (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Constitutional Convention Reunion (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Conventions, National Democratic, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Conventions, State Democratic, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Corporation Commission (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Corporation Commission, Appointments (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Corporation Commission, Appointments, Bristow, M.E. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Corporation Commission, Appointments, Ozlin, Thomas W. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Corporation Commission, Banking Division (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
  - Corporation Commission, Insurance Division (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Corporation Commission, Public Utilities Investigation (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Corporation Commission, Small loans (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cotton (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - County Clerks, Richmond (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - County government Commissions (Box 21, Folder 3-6)
  - County Treasurers (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Accomack County (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Albemarle County (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Alleghany County (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Amherst County (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Arlington County (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Augusta County (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Bath County (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Bland County (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Botetourt County (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Buchanan County (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Buckingham County (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Campbell County (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Carroll County (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Charlotte County (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Clarke County (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Craig County (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Culpeper County (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Cumberland County (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Dickerson County (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Fairfax County (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Fauquier County (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Floyd County (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Fluvanna County (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Giles County (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Gloucester County (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Grayson County (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Henrico County (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Henry County (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Isle of Wight County (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Lancaster County (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Lee County (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Louisa County (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Madison County (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, New Kent County (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Northampton County (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Orange County (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Patrick County (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Powhatan County (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Princess Anne County (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Rappahannock County (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Richmond County (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Roanoke County (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Rockingham County (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Russell County (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Scott County (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Smyth County (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Spotsylvania County (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Wise County (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, Town of Wise (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - County Treasurers, Audits, York County (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - County Treasurers, Fee System (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Cramton dinner (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Crawford, George, Trial (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Criminal expenses (Box 24, Folder 11-12)
  - Criminal expenses, Jail expenses (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Criminal expenses, Trial justices (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Danville strike (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Danville strike (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Davis, Jefferson, Capitol office (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Debate, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Deed books, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Deeds, Commissioner of (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Drought (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
  - Drought (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Eastern baseball championship (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Economy measures (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Education (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
  - Education (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Education, Board Appointments (Box 27, Folder 2-4)
  - Education, Board Appointments, Clement N.E. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Education, Board Appointments, Martin, John (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Education, Commission on Illiteracy (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Education, Co-operative Association (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Education, Financing methods (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Education, General Assembly, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Education, Liberal Arts College for Women (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Education, State Scholarships (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Education, Superintendent of Public Instruction (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
  - Education, Teacher's Retirement Fund (Box 29, Folder 4-6)
  - Education, Teacher's Retirement Fund (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
  - Education, Teacher's salaries (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Education, Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Education, Vocation Rehabilitation (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Election laws, Commission to study (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Examining Boards, Accountancy (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Examining Boards, Banks (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Examining Boards, Bar (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Examining Boards, Dental (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Examining Boards, Embalming (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Examining Boards, Graduate Nurses (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Examining Boards, Medical (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Examining Boards, Optometry (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Examining Boards, Pharmacy (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - Examining Boards, Professional Engineers, Architects, and Land Surveyors (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Examining Boards, Veterinary (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Expenses, Senate committee on (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Family Service Society (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Farmer's National Congress (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Federal Affairs, Agricultural Adjustment Act (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Federal Affairs, Agricultural Credit Conference (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Federal Affairs, Civil Works Administration (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Federal Affairs, Civilian Conservation Corps (Box 33, Folder 2-5)
  - Federal Affairs, Civilian Conservation Corps, Positions (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Federal Affairs, Civilian Conservation Corps, Projects (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Federal Affairs, Emergency Relief, Applications from localities (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Federal Affairs, Emergency Relief, Applications from Individuals (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Federal Affairs, Emergency Relief, Letters to Mayors, Supervisors, etc. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Federal Affairs, Emergency Relief, Meeting, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Federal Affairs, Emergency Relief, New Committee (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Federal Affairs, Emergency Relief, Positions (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Federal Affairs, Farm Loan Board (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Federal Affairs, Home Loan Bank (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Federal Affairs, Legislation (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Federal Affairs, Legislation (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Federal Affairs, Legislation, Cramton Bill (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Federal Affairs, National Employment System (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Federal Affairs, National Industrial Recover Act (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, General (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Director (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Emergency Committee (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Hearings, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 1-5)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Letters (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Planning Board (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Positions (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Projects (Box 36, Folder 9-11)
  - Federal Affairs, Public Works, Wage Scale Committee (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation (Box 37, Folder 1-4)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Applications (Box 37, Folder 5-33)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Applications (Box 38, Folder 1-24)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Applications, Substitute (Box 38, Folder 25-31)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Payments (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Reemployment Service (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Relief (Box 38, Folder 34-36)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Renewals (Box 39, Folder 1-8)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Self-Liquidating, Engineers' Conference (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Self-Liquidating, Personnel (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Self-Liquidating, Projects (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Self-Liquidating, Richmond (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Tennessee Valley Project (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Virginia Relief Committee (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
  - Federal Affairs, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Trade Commission (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner, Recommendations (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner, Recommendations (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Fisheries, Oyster Controversy (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Fisheries, Gloucester War (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Fisheries, Report, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Fisheries, Seafood (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Fisheries, Sponge Crab Bill (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Flags (Box 42, Folder 7-8)
  - Flour (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Foreign representatives (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Forest wardens (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Forester, State (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Forester, State, Chapin-Jones Controversy (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
  - Forestry Commission (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Forestry Commission (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Form letters (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Fort Necessity (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Four-state conference, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Fredericksburg National Battlefield Park (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries (Box 44, Folder 6-9)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Andrews, J.P. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Clarke, Dr. Homer L. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Cooke, Charles B. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Epes, Allan (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Hart, M.D. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Herring, Thomas G. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Massie P.R. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Nolting, C.H. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Sanford, E.W. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Stras, Beverley W., Jr. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Commission, Recommendations, Browne, Beverley F. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Commission, Recommendations, Emmett, Dr. J.M. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Commission, Recommendations, Hening, Dr. T.S. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Commission, Recommendations, Hotchkiss, Henry S. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Garden Club (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Genealogy (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - General Assembly, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - General Assembly, Bills (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Not signed (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Not signed (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Signed (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Messages (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Opinion regarding extra session (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Seafood (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, 1930-1932 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 7-8)
  - General Assembly, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Abutting Assessments (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Barber Board (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Billboards (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Chain stores (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Danville Police Commission (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Delinquent tax (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Firemen's relief (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Moffett fee (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Norfolk Trial Justice (Box 48, Folder 10-11)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Not signed (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Notes on (Box 49, Folder 2-6)